結果は　１位のパリストンが
Now, for verification... Are you Pakunoda, from the Troupe?
有効得票数の過半数を 得られなかったため
Of course. She's telling the truth.
上位８名による再選挙となった
I will present each of you with two conditions.
えっと　敗戦の弁？ 全く負けておりませんけど。
If you abide by them,
I will release your leader.
敬愛するパリストン様によって 実現されます。
Pay attention, Pakunoda.
まぁ　あのじじい… あっ　ネテロね。
He's more concerned about his friends
than killing me for his vengeance.
あれが　むちゃくちゃなのは みんな　ご承知の通り。
That is the chain user's weakness!
あ　もしもし。
However, is there any alternative?
まさかの…　地図ゲットしたよ。
Is there some kind of miracle
飛行船６機分の飛行ルートと 着陸地点が記されてる。
that can get me out of this bind?! There isn't.
残り２機のうち　どちらかに キルア達が乗ってるっぽいね。
I can think of nothing... Yes, this is right.
そっちに画像　送ろうか？
Right now, this is what I should do.
「ドッキリテクスチャー」で ちょっと細工するけど
I must get them back.
大丈夫 こっちにも持ってるバカいたし。
That is my top priority!
ていうか キルアの船は分かってるし。
I don't want to lose
あっそ。
any more friends!
そうか のぞき屋がいるんだっけ
Second, you may not contact
any member of the Troupe.
見られてる 二重尾行されるほど もうろくした覚えは　ないんだが
And to make certain that you adhere to them, I will use my Judgment Chain,
the Arbiter Little Finger, on your leader. You decide if this is acceptable, Pakunoda.
ミッション当初から 時折　感じる何者かの視線 よほど遠くから見ている
Okay.
アマネ　早くおいで　飛ぶよ！ はい！
You're next, Pakunoda.
幸いなことに 夜になって雲が出て来ている キルア様が この機を逃すはずがない
First, release Gon and Killua unharmed,
before midnight, without any tricks. Second, you may not speak
a single word about me.
さすが
If you have no objections,
I will use my chain on you.
遅いね　行くよ！ はい！
Okay.
自らの体をもとに さまざまな乗り物を具現化する これがツボネの能力 「ライダーズハイ」
If Gon and Killua were being
controlled by a Manipulator, could you tell from their heartbeats?
しかし　その原動力は 乗り手のオーラなので
It's certainly possible. I've met Killua-kun, and I know how
his normal heartbeat sounds.
自力では操作できない
So I could tell if anything had changed.
雲の上ならば
That's good enough.
どんなスコープでも 地上から見ることは不可能
I have something to say before the exchange.
アマネ　周囲に 不審な飛行船があったら
Kurapika...
即　迎撃するよ！ はい！ うん　まぁ…
In the back of your mind,
you sense that something is amiss.
どの飛行船も到着まで まだ時間があるし
Why did she come alone?
もう少し　ヒソカを手伝うか。 こちらは異常なし。
If the Troupe were as merciless as expected, this deal would be impossible.
ターゲットは　まだ現れません。
You people are the ones on the ropes.
Ｃ地点から 全く応答がなくなった！ Ａ地点は異常なしだ。
Their rules are ironclad, and their boss accepts them.
応援に行かせるか？
But what about the others?
Ａが無事とは限らない。
This woman appears to be different.
イルミは　針で 人間を操作できるんだろ？ ならば　すでに 事を終えた後かもしれん。
This woman you despise
with everything you have
２０名もの人間を 始末したというのか？
is driven by the same motive that drives you.
アマチュアを何人集めても 無駄ということを
She wishes
針人間のほうを 追っているプロに 警告しておいたほうがいいな。
to save her companion, her boss.
[TEL] ラトゥーンとケンザキから 応答がない。
You must have realized this.
何？ ２人が追ってる 飛行船２機のルートは近い。
Start by returning to your companions. Inform them of the hostage exchange.
恐らく…。 俺が行くしかあるまい。
I want you to bring the hostages to
Lingon Airport before midnight.
清凜隊隊長に足る資質と 度量を見せるチャンスだ！
Bring no one else. Tell no one where you're going. Very well.
投票は　どうする？
You have a deal.
行ける者は 通常通り行くべきだな。
Take me back to the airport.
ハントに出ている者を 差し引いても ４位以内は確実だろう。
Why haven't you asked any questions?
うん　選挙は しっかりと投票しよう。
You know who I am, don't you?
票が読めなくても
You aren't worried?
棄権で投票率を操作するような まねはしたくない。
You don't find this deal unreasonable?
「協専」のハンターを 新たに雇ったらどうだろう？
Do you truly believe I'll return your leader?
我々が現協会のやり方を 引き継ぐ意志を見せておけば
Yes. You wouldn't ask those questions
パリストンに流れている消極票を 削れるかもしれない。
if you intended to deceive me.
うまく行けば 「協専」の連中も敵にやられて
Does he really expect us to
accept those conditions?
次の投票で欠席になってくれる かもしれないからな
Tell us where he is, Pakunoda.
まぁ　これを言ったら
We'll kill the kids, then deal
with the chain user.
テラデインは 断固反対するだろうが
You're insisting? I insist.
票の動向が読めない時は 積極的に棄権して
If you don't tell us, I won't let you leave.
無効にしておくべきなのに テラデインは愚直で ブシドラは大ざっぱ過ぎる
I refuse to tell you where he is,
and I am taking the kids alone. Don't interfere. Interfere?
テラデインさんから 「協専」と同じ条件で依頼が？
Who's the one interfering with our plans?! Go, Pakunoda.
素晴らしい！ いいじゃないですか！
We'll stop them. Stop us?
受けましょうよ　やってください！
Are you trying to insult us?
私に遠慮や気遣いは無用です。
You're serious? I don't get it.
むしろ 雇用人数に制限がないのなら
Have you lost your minds?
積極的に声を掛けて 皆さんで参加してください。
I bet they were defeated by the
chain user before we arrived.
仕事をしてみて気付いたことや 見習ってほしいことがあれば
They're probably under his control. This is a waste of time.
どんどん私に連絡をください。
I'll make them talk.
その上で改善すべき点があれば 迅速に変えて行きますから。
Is it really so hard to understand?
フッ。 フフフ…。
You don't understand why
Machi is stopping you?
いや　いいトリオですね。
You honestly think they're being controlled?
好きだな。
They want to rescue your boss!
分かりやすくて。
Is it so hard to understand
the desire to save a friend?
投票率９１．２％で不成立。
Are you that desperate to be spared?
どういうことだ!?
I'm not doing this for my sake.
テラデイン　全滅だ！
Take back those words!
針人間を追っていた 俺達のメンバーや撮影隊
Good grief.
「協専」の連中も！
I refuse.
If you've a problem, come here.
ブシドラも！ えっ！　バカな！
The second you take a step,
I'll rip your head off. Then I won't budge an inch!
強力な兵隊を雇ってるに 違いない！
Kurapika isn't like you.
１人ですけど。
No matter how much he hates someone, he wouldn't lose control and
kill them without mercy. If he makes a promise, he will definitely keep his word!
上空を飛行してからは 視線を感じない
After meeting him in person,
Pakunoda knows this.
やはり途中までは 追尾されてたってことだね
If you follow his conditions,
he'll return your boss! That's enough, kid...
晴れちゃったな
Don't think you can say anything you want! That's enough.
まぁ　これだけ病院から 離れてれば　大丈夫だろ
Let Pakunoda go. You're siding with them?
病院に入る時　誰かにアルカの 姿を見られてしまったら
Shal, right now, what would our
worst-case scenario be?
ツボネは　アルカの能力の示唆に 当たると判断して 強制帰宅の執行を 即決するだろう かといって 周辺の人払いを徹底したら
The boss is already dead, Pakunoda and the others are being controlled, we can't find the chain user, and the two kids escape...
イルミの格好の標的になる
Then, you've got it wrong.
このまま病院へ飛行船で 接近することは　困難だな
The worst-case scenario would be that
we all die and the spider perishes.
やっぱり 車で病院内部まで入るという
By comparison, your scenario
would be quite pleasant.
ゴトーのやり方がベストだな
Am I wrong?
[TEL] ん？
N-No, you're right.
[TEL]
I don't care about your reasons.
You're being too reliant on the boss.
カナリア？　ゴトーと 連絡　取れないんだけど…。 [TEL]　私もです。 それじゃ　これから言う３か所に
If the Troupe falls apart as a result, that's the greatest betrayal you
could make toward the boss.
代わりの車を 大至急　向かわせるよう
If we keep bickering, that could well happen.
お前からヒシタ達に言ってくれ。
Cool off.
かしこまりました。
Let them have their way...
雲の上を飛ぶことで 下の人間は完全にまいたはず 車に乗るまでは問題ない
If the boss doesn't return, we kill the members being controlled,
and start to rebuild the spider.
あとは　病院までのルートだな
It's extremely simple. I'm fine with that. If that's what it takes to satisfy you.
ゴン 待ってろよ！
Well, I'm not being controlled,
and it won't be easy to kill me.
オッケー ナイスタイミングだ　ヒシタ。
Are you okay? Are they there?
大回りしたせいで 時間は　かかったけど
Yeah, they're all here. Hey!
病院から６０ｋｍも離れてるんだ 見つかるはずがない。
We're following your orders.
病院まで行ってくれ。 かしこまりました。
Aren't you going to follow them? The chain user can't monitor our location now.
どうした？ 前に　人が。 あれは…　針人間！
For now, I'll just sit and wait. If the boss fails to return, I'll kill you, too. Go ahead.
まさか　なぜ？ 俺達をつけるのは不可能
Board the waiting airship.
車か？ この車をつけてたのか？
The pilot already has his orders. As promised, it's just the three of them.
ヒシタ！　ぶっ飛ばして行け！
We can't be sure until the airship takes off.
あいつらは　もう　助からない！
Stay alert.
無理です　キルア様。
There's someone over there.
イルミ様のご命令がないと。
That's
なっ…　何!?
Hisoka! Hi... Why are you here?!
完全に囲まれてる あっ
Hurry up. Without needles, I can only change
my face for four to five hours.
バカな なぜ　ここにいる？
Allow me on the airship with them. If you refuse, I'll kill Gon and Killua.
イルミ　なぜ！
Bastard... Just kidding. That would be such a waste.
不可能だろ 俺達の乗っている飛行船が どれか分かってなきゃ
My target is the boss.
いや　違う 分かってても無理なんだ
Once he's released, I'll get off the airship.
雲の上を数十ｋｍ飛行してる 地上から追えるはずがない
I want to fight him. That's all I want.
俺１人なら　何とでもなる
Killua, place the phone next to your heart.
けど　アルカを 無傷でとなると厳しい
It's fine, nothing's wrong with him.
なぜ　ここが分かった？ 教えたら　アルカを こちらに渡してくれるかい？
Okay, let's begin the exchange!
呼ぶしかない ナニカを
If you talk to or make any contact
with a Troupe member, you die.
私ですよ。
Now you will get to experience the pain
まんまと一杯食わされた 間抜けはね。
of losing your home.
あ　ツボネだ！ 私のスコープを 通して見える映像を
I've waited a long time for this moment.
奥様が屋敷で見ておられます。
Now... Let's do this.
ピンポン　のぞき屋はツボネ。
I no longer need this.
雲が切れると同時に また視線を感じるようになって ようやく気付きました。
This won't be considered an internal spat now, so you needn't hold back.
いや　まさか 盗撮の気配にまで気付くとは
I see.
さすがツボネ。
You aren't a Troupe member,
so we can talk. I can't fight you.
まぁ　バレたところで 母さんの指令なんだから
Rather, I'm not worth fighting.
スコープは外せないだろう。 ええ おっしゃる通りでございます。
He used his Judgment Chain on my heart.
ツボネ。 中指の爪　ちょうだい。
I can no longer use my Nen.
ええ　喜んで。
We can leave. Oh...
はい　坊ちゃま！
Hisoka returned to the airship without fighting.
ツボネ　薬指の爪　ちょうだい。
The leader realized that Hisoka
wasn't a Troupe member, so he explained about my chains.
はいな お安いご用でございますことよ。
I'm not surprised that Hisoka wasn't interested in fighting someone without Nen.
ツボネ　感謝するぜ
He wasn't a Troupe member? No. How did you sneak out?
さぁ　キルア様 好きに「お願い」なさいませ。
I no longer have any reason to kill Chrollo.
尻拭いは 私とアマネがいたしますことよ。
I'm not interested in broken toys.
キルア様の足を 引っ張ってしまった罪滅ぼし。
"You can slip out now..." There. That's right. My real fortune mentioned
後生ですから させてくださいませ。
I would have a date with the boss on Tuesday.
できるのかい？　ならいいよ。 それは　ゴンの時の「お願い」も
And when I left, the Troupe was supposed to be
down to half its members.
その順序で やってくれるってことだよね？
Fate appears to be changing, bit by bit.
俺を殺すために その２人を犠牲にできるなら
I'm sorry for putting you in danger.
ゴンを救うために　見知らぬ大勢を 犠牲にすることも平気だろう。
Nah... You used your chains on the boss, right? Yeah, but...
ルール５ 同じ人間が連続して 「お願い」することはできない
This isn't the end.
イルミを敵に回すほうが 楽しいか
Meow.
迷うね
Where's the boss? He won't be coming here.
「うん」と言ってくれれば 俺は喜んで死ぬよ？
Don't mess with me.
Explain yourself! Depending on your response...
お前のインナーミッション 大成功だろう？
Don't worry. In return...
家族間での殺しは　ご法度だけど お前が「お願い」する　それは…
I can only shoot six bullets at once. That's enough for the
remaining founding members.
家族じゃないからね。
Feitan. Phinks.
仮にルール５が裏ルールで キルアには通用しなくても
Franklin.
俺が死んで残る家族がセーフなら それでもいいさ
Do you trust me?
キルアは生涯　苦しむだろう
Paku, you can't mean to...
俺は　キルアの心の中で 永遠に生き続ける
Hey, are you being controlled by— Phinks! Have some faith.
さぁ　やりなよ。
It's Paku.
これは取引だぞ。
My memories...
キル　俺の死と ゴンについての「お願い」を お前自身でするとを
My feelings...
交換だ。
I pass them all to you.
ゴンが元に戻っても プラマイゼロじゃない？
Please...
それなら
Let all this
アルカを殺って キルアに憎まれて
end with me... Paku.
ナニカ。
I understand everything.
ツボネの左手を治してくれ。
Pakunoda was...
ん…。 手…　手…。
I hope Kurapika's fever doesn't break.
ツボネ　左手　出して。
Yeah... Wait, did you just say what I think you said?
キルア様　しかし…。 いいから。
Kurapika shouldn't fight the Troupe anymore.
ナニカは壊すのは得意だけど 治すのは苦手だ。
If he'd just wanted revenge, he would have chosen different abilities. Really?
治す時は それに直接　触れる必要がある。 けど…。
If he'd only wanted to kill them, he wouldn't have gone to the
trouble of chaining their hearts.
お。
Maybe if he only had one target.
あい。 キルア　いい子いい子して！
But Kurapika's dealing with the entire Troupe.
もちろん　いいよ。
Even if he captures one,
he can't kill them right away.
すごいな　ナニカ。
And he needs to extract information
about the other members.
エヘヘヘ…。
Oh... Personally, I think his powers were meant
specifically for revenge.
俺をキルアって呼ぶのはナニカだ。
Oh...
治すのは疲れるんだろうな。
But that was his original objective.
すぐ寝ちゃう。
Kurapika is different now.
だけど　これだけだ。 ナニカに何かを治す 「お願い」をした後で
I have good friends...
ナニカが残酷な見返りを 求めたことなんか　一度もない！
But you do have a point. I'd prefer him to stay still for a while.
ナニカは　誰より優しいよ。 呪われてるのは 「お願い」するほうだ。
If their boss doesn't come back, they'll be even more
determined to find Kurapika. Yeah. We'll have to be extremely careful
今度　ナニカを それ呼ばわりしてみろ。
when we go to the auction house.
貴様を兄貴とは思わない。
So, do you really have a plan for
obtaining a copy of Greed Island ?
分かったよ　キル。
Y-Yeah, but it's a fifty-fifty deal. Originally, didn't you say it had
a seventy percent chance?
お前にリスクが及ばずに ゴンを治せるなら
I get it... That's clever.
それに越したことはない。
Actually, that may be our only shot.
だけど　ナニカが危険な存在なのは 何一つ変わっちゃいないし
Realistic and sound. I think it has an eighty percent chance!
俺の疑問が 解消されたわけでもない。
Really? Yeah, we can make it work!
キル　お前は まだ　何か隠している。
The auction is in Hall B.
ミルキのルール５が お前に当てはまらないのも　そう。
That way. Over there.
全てを話さない限り アルカは解放されないよ。
Wow! Huh?
バカ だから話せねえんだろうが
Why are they here?
最後のルールを知ったら
How would I know?!
お前は…　いや　お前らは
Hey, that was cold. No need to run away.
喜んで俺の頭に　また
Why wouldn't we run away? Don't worry.
針を埋めに来るだろうよ
We're not going to kill you.
キルア様 病院へお連れいたします。
Because we can't kill the chain user now. Huh? What do you mean? Huh?
[TV] 清凜隊同志のブシドラ隊長が
Didn't he use his chains on the boss?
今回の悪辣ハンターの追跡中に
That means we can't kill him. Why not? Isn't it the other way around?
敵の手によって殺害されました。 [TV]　我々の身内に　残忍な悪魔が 交じっていることは
It's pretty useful to have someone
who's willing to ask questions.
もう　疑いようがありません。
Nen doesn't necessarily disappear after death.
[TV]　しかし　誠に遺憾ながら 現在の清凜隊に
Nen that's driven by hatred and regret
can persist a long time after death.
奴…　もしくは奴らを捕らえ 法の場へ引きずり出す 力はありません。
That Nen will direct itself toward
the target of those emotions.
[TV]　皆さん！ これは協会が一丸となって 即刻に解決せねばならない 最優先事項です！
Since the boss can no longer use Nen, he could be overwhelmed by that assault.
[TV]　そのためにも ぜひとも我々は今回の選挙で
Residual Nen can be quite fearsome.
投票率９５％以上
That's why we can't kill the chain user.
最多得票者過半数超えを 果たしたいと考えております。
I'm talking too much?
[TV]　そこで我々は　前会長派とも パイプの太いモラウ氏に
I know. I won't say another word. There are Nen users
隊長の要請を打診し 現在　交渉中です。 [TV]　それと同時に 次なる悲劇を防ぐために
who can remove other people's Nen.
悪魔の実名と顔写真
East, huh...
その能力などを 公表する用意ができております。
So, we're done with you kids.
[TV]　我々の趣旨　意向に 賛同される方は　どうか！
We just came to enjoy the auction.
[TV]　このテラデインに 一票を投じていただきたい！
The other members wanted to go home. Um, what happened to Pakunoda-san?
あ　えっと…。
She died.
まず　その話　断ったよな？
Huh? Oh...
考え直してはくれんか？ [TEL]　確かに俺は 前会長とは親しかったし
Why don't you run away?
アリ討伐にも参加した。
Run away?
[TEL]　…が　決して武闘派じゃ　ねえ。
Given my injuries, you should
be able to escape.
[TEL]　作戦の性質上 サポート能力として 俺に白羽の矢が立っただけで 自分を強いとも思ってねえ。
If you did, I would lose my leverage, and the chain user could kill the boss. So why don't you run away?
しかし…。
Aren't you on his side?
ベスト１６の紹介　見ただろう！
Because we're his friends.
俺は　シーハンター もともとは海の人　海人。
Because we're his friends,
we don't want him to kill.
陸に上げてどうする！ [TEL]　そこを曲げて…。 [TEL]　そもそも選挙を 即行で終わらせたいなら
So we'd prefer this to be
settled with an exchange.
お前らの票を全部　パリストンに ぶち込めば済む話だろうが。
What's wrong?
[TEL]　まぁ　俺は死んでも あいつには入れねえがな。
Let's go. Paku...
最後に言っとくが そいつの情報公開したら お前さん達は　もちろん
Paku wanted to thank you.
[TEL]　それから　清凜隊 名乗ってんじゃ　ねえ！ [TEL]　弱えぇくせに。 [TEL]　人の忠告を全く聞かねえ おたくらと組む気はねえし
Next week, the story moves
into the Greed Island arc.